<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-01-28T19:38:40+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">memsec</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">Purpose and Goal</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2022/01/25/purpose-and-goal.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Purpose and Goal" /><published>2022-01-25T20:24:56+01:00</published><updated>2022-01-25T20:24:56+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2022/01/25/purpose-and-goal</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2022/01/25/purpose-and-goal.html">&lt;p&gt;memsec comprises of two security enthusiasts with backgrounds in security and software development, located in Scandinavia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aiming to further develop and master the craft of identifying security risks and software faults, our end goal is to better understand and share the impact exposed security vulnerabilities can
have on operational systems and organizations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;memsec’s scope in the security realm is focused on OT security, this includes operational systems, modern industry, smart devices and IOT as opposed to more traditional IT security.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">memsec comprises of two security enthusiasts with backgrounds in security and software development, located in Scandinavia. Aiming to further develop and master the craft of identifying security risks and software faults, our end goal is to better understand and share the impact exposed security vulnerabilities can have on operational systems and organizations. memsec’s scope in the security realm is focused on OT security, this includes operational systems, modern industry, smart devices and IOT as opposed to more traditional IT security.</summary></entry></feed>